[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
It's nice to see you both here. Two brothers together.
All right, well, Director Baek, let me pour you a drink.
I heard your little brother was a standout,
even way back during his tenure at the Military Academy.
You must be very proud.
He's a work in progress.
You were kind to have him at this important gathering.
Really, I'm grateful.
Oh, come on. It's a casual get-together.
An opportunity to get a couple of Academy alumni together and catch up.
And I've been so impressed by what my men have been able to accomplish lately.
I put this little thing together to show my full appreciation.
Oh, by the way. I heard a rumor. You two go way back, isn't that right?
Oh, yes.
At this point, I don't know if it's fate or a curse,
but Director Baek keeps following me around.
You know, maybe we were tortured lovers in another life or something.
-[laughs] -[chuckles]
Right, who knows.
You'd think we'd be sick of each other.
I guess some ties can't be severed so easily.
You know what I mean, Advisor Jang?
You like me that much, huh?
Yes, you're all I think about.
Eventually, even the thread that holds us together will get cut.
Things happen in life only when they're meant to.
You can't impose your plans on it.
I'm amazed how little you've changed, Baek.
Still a gentleman on the surface,
but vicious underneath.
Like some dog acting like he doesn't bite, right?
You haven't changed much either.
A few drinks and you're smashed, aren't you?
I can't hold my liquor, that's true.
Here. [grunts]
Go ahead, let me pour you another.
Colonel Baek.
I wish you would've told me
that your older brother was going to show up.
I suppose this was a mistake. Clearly I'm not welcome here.
All I wanted was to have a drink on this important occasion.
Well, then…
Can I speak to you?
[Hwang] Hey, now.
Wait a minute, please.
If you leave the table now…
I'm gonna cry.
-[laughs] -[all laughing]
Hey, come on. Stay.
This alcohol isn't good enough.
Colonel Ahn, where's the most expensive bottle?
We can't serve Director Baek subpar booze.
Sure thing, sir. I'll get the best bottle.
You like hard liquor, don't you?
I have a feeling you drank plenty when the President was around.
Yeah, but…
the price of the bottle isn't what matters, right?
It's more about who you're drinking with.
Wow, spoken like a true gentleman, huh?
You know something?
Director Baek never gets drunk, no matter how much he drinks.
It's amazing.
Whoa, that's incredible.
I guess someone's a pro at holding his liquor, huh?
[Jaeho] Take your pick, Commander.
[Hwang] All right, Director Baek, let me pour you a nice big glass of Chivas.
Ah, right.
[Hwang] You too, Advisor Jang.
Ah, sure.
Would you like one, Colonel?
I would be grateful, sir. Much appreciated.
You should have one too.
Oh, if you insist.
All right, now that we have someone so distinguished at our table,
I want to savor the moment. [chuckles]
Everybody ready?
-[guest 1] Yes! -[guest 2] Let's do it!
-[Hwang] All right, then. -[ticking]
[Hwang] Great.
[Hwang] Well, regardless of whatever has happened
between us up until now,
starting today, we are united.
Am I right?
-[officers] Yes! -Okay, then.
We are!
[officers] We are one!
Now that you've had a drink, you should give us a song.
Come on, bring in the band.
-[laughs] -Get the band. Come on, Nami.
Wow, who knew you were such a partier.
-[in English] Colonel, hold on. Just stop. -[band stops]
Just a minute.
[sighs] Don't spoil the lively mood with some old army song.
Know anything else?
I only know military tunes, sir. Sorry about that.
Ugh, no. [clicks tongue]
All right, forget it. Give me the mic.
-[ticking] -[officers exclaim, laugh]
Man, right when I came off my tour of Southeast Asia.
[Jaeho] All right, all right. The commander's taking the mic!
One, two, three, and!
[Jaeho] Girl!
[Jaeho] At first!
[Jaeho] Beautiful!
[Kihun, in English] Now, if you cut this red wire, the countdown will stop.
It has to be the red wire.
If you cut the blue one by mistake, it'll go off immediately.
[in English] Sing it!
-[singing fades] -[ticking]
[Kitae, in English] A single mistake could bring everything to an end.
That's why you have to put your life on the line,
because every move could be your last.
[Kitae] The truth is, it might only be sheer luck
that you've survived as long as you have.
-Then again… -[ticking stops]
…maybe it's fate.
-[applause] -[Hwang] All right, let's keep it going!
-Colonel Ahn, you're up next! -[all cheering]
[Jaeho] It's my honor, sir!
So, how did it go?
Motherfucker.
Everyone out.
Hey, get out. Come on, out!
Shit, shit.
-[knocks on door] -[door opens]
Director.
The bomb's gone missing.
It wasn't there.
I don't know what happened.
[shouting] What do you mean it's gone, you idiot?
Could Pyo have taken it?
I've been keeping tabs on him, sir, and there's been no contact with Jang.
It's a slim possibility.
Do you think your brother could've…
Sir, your brother could've taken it.
Did he seem like he knew something yesterday?
If Jang had it, he'd be trying to make moves on you already.
Maybe you should go talk to your brother.
I heard you were there, Colonel Baek.
Where?
General Hwang's special meeting.
So, how was it?
Uneventful. He just thanked us for our hard work.
Still, it's a pretty exclusive group, right?
A guy like me with no connections wouldn't get invited in a million years.
I'll be quiet.
Let's go.
-[phone ringing] -[typewriter keys clacking]
Morning, Chief.
Oh, Baek. Who's this?
He'll be assisting with American military affairs from now on.
Yes, sir! Captain Min Jonghwan.
Well, Baek. You must be pretty busy.
Look, the guy's smart. Take him under your wing for me.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
-Hey. -Yes, sir.
Ever smoked American cigarettes?
Sorry?
They're hard to come by. Just take one and be grateful.
-Take it. -Yes, sir. Much appreciated.
-Baek, you want one or what? -No, I'll pass.
Right.
You probably have plenty of rare commodities
stocked up at your brother's place.
How's your sister? Feeling any better?
I'm sorry, I heard she's in the hospital.
I'm asking because I'm genuinely worried about her.
Why?
Don't wanna miss your chance to interrogate her?
No, that's not why…
Okay, never mind.
When she wakes up, just… let me know.
About yesterday…
why do you think he showed up?
Because he was scared. You saw him.
He skulked up to the table like a little mutt
with his tail between his legs. [chuckles]
The man's an expert at backstabbing.
Can't trust a word out of his mouth.
I guess you're right.
You know, at the KCIA, the first thing they teach you there is how to lie.
Baek Kitae must be one slippery little bastard, to say the least.
That slick piece of shit.
Okay, Jang.
Here's where I'm at. Just my opinion on our circumstances.
Right now, the KCIA and the MSC are basically performing the same job.
Why do we need both of them?
It's a complete waste, for the government and the taxpayers.
We gotta come up with a way to fix that, don't we?
Say the word and I'm on it.
I'll have Baek Kitae brought in.
I've mentioned before
that I won't bring the guy in on meth charges.
What's his deal?
DEPUTY DIRECTOR PYO HAKSU
-[humming] -[door opens]
What brings you here?
You're still running ops to gather intel, right?
Of course.
I'm not gonna stop because of the JIH.
Without those, the KCIA's screwed.
-And this is what you have on them? -Yeah.
We should know their people, shouldn't we?
You want to sit?
One thing I've learned is Hwang Daesik really looks after his own.
Anyone from his school or hometown,
he holds them close. One big family.
OFFICER PERSONNEL… RANK: LIEUTENANT COLONEL / BAEK KIHYUN
I told my guys to investigate everybody.
Some clueless idiot threw Colonel Baek in there too.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Send this to my office. All of it.
Why?
You never cared about this stuff.
Do it.
Very good.
That bastard barks another damn order at me, I swear I'm gonna…
[whispering] Go ahead, come on back here, you prick. That's right.
You want me to send all the files, you motherfucker?
Shut your mouth, Baek, you big, slimy piece of shit.
You can't just keep kicking me around.
Yeah, move it, don't mess with me.
Shut your mouth, you bitch.
I'm gonna take your chair. Check this out.
How about that?
Where the hell are you going?
You didn't pick up the phone.
Have something you wanna say?
Yeah, why were you there?
Well, I might ask you the same question.
What exactly were you trying to pull there,
in front of that many people?
You must've had some plan.
-[sighs] -Don't try anything funny.
If you do, I'll bring you in myself.
You will always be the brother of Baek Kitae.
Jang Geonyoung is using you. He'll chew you up and spit you out!
Look, times have changed.
The KCIA is on its way out.
Chief Cheon's case is hopeless. He's done for.
But it's not too late for you to walk away and go to Japan.
I'll be there for Soyeong and Minju.
You don't trust me anymore? Is that what you're saying?
You've never been able to trust me.
-[door closes] -[sighs]
Wow. It looks so great, Kihyun.
It screams "top of your class."
[loudly] He's top of his class, do you hear that?
-Soyeong. -Hmm?
-I'm sorry. -Sorry for what?
Just… all of it.
Try to listen to Kitae. I'll be all right. Hmm?
Just wait a little longer.
As soon as I'm finished with school,
I'll work hard and give you the greatest life.
-You mean it? -Yeah.
I'll always take care of you, don't worry. I'll protect our family.
Come on, you're still just a kid.
Take care of yourself and eat plenty of food, you got that?
Mm-hmm.
-[Kitae] Come on, you'll miss the train. -Yes, sir.
-Go inside. It's cold. -All right, all right.
-Go on. [chuckles] -Yeah, I heard you. [chuckles]
Write me, star cadet! Don't forget!
-[egg cracks] -[exclaims]
You did well.
Mom and Dad would be proud.
And I don't say that lightly.
What is it? Soyeong, you okay?
Come on, here.
It's okay.
[Kitae] When did you wake up?
You better? You feeling all right?
Why did you do it?
Didn't I tell you to stay away from that stuff?
You been on it for a while?
Does Minju ever see you like this?
Give me a break. You made a fortune from meth.
I'm sure you know a lot about us junkies.
[whispers] Help me out.
You can get me some, can't you?
Just one last time. I swear. I swear, all right? I swear.
Gimme one more little bump. Just one more time--
-[shouting] Are you outta your mind? -Stop it! Don't yell at me!
Okay? You have no right to raise your voice! Got it?
Minju's father is dead 'cause of you.
You killed him, right? I heard everything. You killed Daeil, didn't you?
Who told you that?
[sobbing] Poor Daeil…
What did Daeil ever do to deserve that? Huh?
[sobbing] Everything you told us to do,
we bent over backwards for it, like idiots.
You son of a bitch.
[shouting] How could you do this to us?
Do you know what it was like for me to have Minju? Do you?
Do you have any idea how hard it's been?
Do you know what I've been through all these years?
Oh, Daeil, that poor man.
Don't worry about anything.
Minju still needs you.
Try to accept the treatment…
then you'll be on your feet soon.
[Soyeong] Don't come back here.
-[sobs] -Soyeong.
[sobs] Just pretend I'm dead.
Don't you ever come see me again!
[crying] I'm such…
such an idiot.
[sobbing] I'm such an idiot!
I can't face her like this! How will I ever look at Minju again?
Commander, we appreciate you having us over to your home, sir.
I mean, it's subpar, I'd say.
I was never good at putting money aside, honestly.
I wouldn't have been able to afford this house
if my wife hadn't budgeted so well.
-[chuckles] How 'bout that. -It's the truth.
Colonel Baek.
The house may not look too great,
but I'm gonna make sure you eat as much as you want.
Yes, sir. Much appreciated.
Here, how about a drink?
You've been working hard
to dig up more information on Chief Cheon's slush fund, I take it.
Since you trusted me with it, I have to give it my all.
He's the best man for it.
I know it involves your family. That's difficult.
Still, Baek, I'm willing to bet you're the man for this investigation.
I'll do my very best.
Great! We are…
-One. -One.
Ah, geez.
If we're gonna have special guests over, we should be serving something special.
My wife never listens.
Let's see.
Okay, here we go. [grunts]
Hey, Colonel Ahn, grab this kettle here.
Yes, sir, I'm on it.
All right, Kihyun. [grunts]
Check out this piece of work. Eh?
A guy a couple years below me at the Academy sent it over.
He got injured during training, and then, he had to resign.
And now he's out in the middle of nowhere growing ginseng.
Chungsik, sir? He was my classmate.
That's right. You were in the same year, weren't you?
Yes, we were.
This here? Chungsik actually made this himself.
Are you sure you want to share something so valuable, sir?
The man sends me a new one every single year.
He's got three kids,
and I put all three through college.
I was happy to do it.
So that pot of honey, was that from an officer as well?
Sure was.
That stuff is priceless, can't get it anywhere.
And at the end of the day, it's the thought that counts.
[Jaeho] You're right, sir.
You have something of a reputation for looking after young officers.
How do you manage to support and take care of so many?
I have a question.
What do you think it means to be a soldier?
To be loyal to the country and to be devoted to its defense.
Correct.
Loyalty and devotion.
A soldier puts his mortal life on the line.
And how do you think it feels
when your country doesn't recognize that? Huh?
Every soldier needs someone that acknowledges their sacrifice.
[inhales] To that end…
if you say you've got my back…
then I will have yours to the bitter end.
You understand?
And your family is included, too.
[Geonyoung] One scoop of creamer…
and one scoop of sugar.
That's it.
I've tried it a few different ways,
and I've discovered this is the perfect balance…
-[spoon clinks] -…for this brew.
Okay. Here you go.
[slurps] Ah.
Ah, that's nice. [laughs]
All the assemblymen who used to treat you like royalty…
I've talked to them, you know?
I interrogated them one by one.
Understand?
They're the kind of people that love clinging to power when they can,
but suddenly, the moment it's gone, they all scatter like roaches.
Classic opportunists.
We both know that power comes and goes.
It can be elusive as the wind.
Even the mighty Korean oak sheds its leaves eventually.
Hwang Daesik won't be around forever.
So you like… oak trees?
Careful, one wrong move with me, you'll get chopped up for kindling.
-Hmm? -[scoffs]
All right, why don't you throw in the towel
while you still have some dignity?
Come on, you were a guy with influence,
standing right next to the most important men in Korea.
Want to spend the rest of your life rotting on the forest floor?
Have some self-respect. You're through.
Turn Baek Kitae in and confess.
You shoved my head into the crapper, Mister Jang.
My self-respect is long gone.
I wonder what you're hoping for. [chuckles]
Why bide your time, Chief Cheon?
I know there's a reason you're holding out.
Know what, why don't I just take a guess?
I think you're waiting.
You're waiting for…
Hwang Daesik to die.
Busted.
Pyo Haksu just compiled these dossiers.
They're all members of the JIH.
OFFICER PERSONNEL RECORD
Why don't you take a look for potential new informants?
Yes, Director Baek.
Sir, I've been wondering…
what did Colonel Baek say?
Did he put it together?
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of it.
Why do you think he didn't tell us he was going to be there?
I don't understand, sir. If…
if our strategy was exposed beforehand, wouldn't that mean…
I apologize.
-Kihun… -Yes, Director?
We need…
more explosives, right away.
Huh?
We do?
You start something, you have to finish it.
With all due respect, we lost the last batch, sir.
Someone's already aware of this.
And that means we have to hurry and finish it.
That's how…
we survive this.
-[phone ringing] -[typewriter keys clacking]
Colonel Baek.
You had dinner last night, at General Hwang's house.
-Is that true? -Yes.
[Geonyoung] Okay. Well?
Have you made a decision?
Made a decision about what, sir?
Hold on.
You're still making up your mind? Really?
You playing Hamlet or something? Huh?
Sit down for a second.
[grunts] Right, I'll be direct with you.
Let's talk about your brother.
I want to know why he showed up at Heaven Cloud Pavilion.
You know, don't you?
He showed up, out of nowhere.
Can you tell me why?
You're thinking the same thing I am, aren't you?
I think we have the exact same theory.
Baek Kitae…
was trying to take out…
General Hwang Daesik.
But then,
all of a sudden, his little brother showed up.
You threw a wrench into it.
Do you have any proof?
That he did any of that?
If I had solid proof…
you think I'd be dumb enough to let him walk?
Don't go around accusing people without any proof.
I'm only saying this out of the goodness of my heart.
The entire KCIA has already been credibly accused
of conspiring to assassinate the President, Colonel.
If Baek Kitae tries…
to kill General Hwang, you know what that means,
don't you?
You and your entire family… are done.
Oh, that will never happen.
It better not.
-[Min] Sorry to interrupt, sir. -Mmm.
Director Baek suddenly showed up.
Wants to see his brother, huh?
Actually… he says he wants to speak with you.
Ah, so he's here to have a chat with me, not Colonel Baek, huh?
[Min] Yes, sir.
Director Baek, good to see you.
I'll show you inside.
Afternoon, sir!
This way, sir.
-Captain Min. -Yes, sir.
JOINT INVESTIGATION HEADQUARTERS INVESTIGATION DIVISION
Shall we step inside?
This way, please.
Well, hello, Prosecutor.
Can I… help you, Director Baek?
Watch yourself if you wanna live.
-Yes? -It's Colonel Ahn Jaeho, sir.
[Geonyoung] Come in.
All right, Colonel.
Give us a little privacy.
Yes, of course.
What brings you here?
Well, I heard they gathered the finest operatives in Korea…
so I thought I'd come by and take a look around.
[Geonyoung] And? What do you think?
They're all here to bring down an evil prick like you.
All this for me, huh?
Hwang Daesik really put this operation together
just to catch one lousy guy?
Why are you here, Baek?
Leave Kihyun alone. I'd really appreciate it.
That's pretty polite for a threat.
If you screw with my family, I'll hurt yours.
You piece of shit.
Wow, you'll hurt anybody as long as it's not your own flesh and blood.
If you're afraid for them, then stop this.
That's how you protect your loved ones.
Put an end to it.
Do you really think I can stop at this point?
There was this officer once.
This was back in the army. And, whew, this bastard gave me hell.
He was always smacking me around, cursing me out.
I must have made a good punching bag for him,
'cause my family had no connections.
So I wondered what kind of rich, privileged household
this asshole came from that entitled him to act like that.
Turns out this guy had no connections either. [chuckles]
He was raised in a dirt-poor family. They had nothing.
People looked down on them constantly.
And this poor bastard was picked on like crazy.
That's why he couldn't resist
making life hard for people who were just like him.
Two losers who were born with jack shit,
ripping each other apart for the hell of it.
Know what I thought…
when that son of a bitch would start beating the shit out of me?
"First I'll kill this asshole, then I'll kill myself"?
That's right.
"This sick bastard is going down.
Then I'll follow."
You know exactly what that feels like.
Baek Kitae.
I already lived through that once.
You think I'm going to let it happen again?
If you don't pump the brakes and stop what you're doing,
neither will I.
This only ends when one of us is dead.
Wow, that's dramatic.
I hear you.
Now let me ask you a favor, Mr. Jang.
Let me see Chief Cheon immediately.
His whole family's been very worried.
I mean, he's not even allowed visitors.
His wife came to see me the other day and begged me to try to help.
Can you make that happen?
Just a brief chat.
We found Park Changbae.
…SCENE INVESTIGATION REPORT ON BODY FOUND
[Yejin] His body was dumped up in the hills.
It's Baek Kitae.
He made this happen.
He's on a mission to wipe out every last trace of his drug operation.
But what's his angle right now?
He had to have come into the office for a reason.
-[sighs] -[groans]
So how are you holding up, sir?
I'm all right.
And how about you?
You look like a million bucks.
Your wife is upset. She's worried about you.
Why is she worried?
I'm still eating and shitting. Tell my wife to relax.
And remind her to walk Gaettong when she can.
If that little mutt doesn't get his exercise…
he gets ferocious.
Yes, I'll remind her.
Are there any other messages you want me to pass along?
Lend me a smoke. [grunts]
There's one other thing.
My father's memorial is coming up, but I…
haven't cleaned up his grave since Chuseok.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Really?
I'd appreciate that very much.
When you gonna do it?
[on speakers] The grass must be pretty overgrown by now.
If you're going to take care of it, you should get it done soon.
I'm on it, sir. I'll do it this week.
Okay, that's perfect.
The weeds are gonna be pretty tough at this point.
Just pull them all out.
Yes, sir. I will.
Doesn't that sound a little suspicious?
What does?
[Yejin] I mean…
Well, I don't know.
The way they're talking.
What's suspicious about it?
Baek Kitae…
is just offering to help clean up his father's grave site.
People do each other favors like that all the time.
Did you see him, sir?
Uh-huh.
Do you think that Jang suspects anything?
Um, sir?
What do we do?
Continue as planned.
-Are you sure? -[agent sniffles] Yes, sir.
I have a buddy in Foreign Intelligence. He told me himself.
An order came through not long ago.
They must've had trouble getting a new round of explosives.
-Hey. -Yes, sir? [sniffles]
-What's with the sniffling? -Sorry, sir.
Sinus infection.
-You. -Yes, sir?
Find out what they're for.
When, where, and how they're gonna use those.
I'll take care of it.
Find out for sure.
-Yes, sir. -Go.
Baek Kitae, that bastard.
Sly little shit.
[Kitae] Captain Min Jonghwan.
You know who I am?
Yes.
I, uh…
Where am I, sir?
And what am I doing here?
You telling me you really don't know?
No, I'm sorry, sir.
I really have no idea what you're talking about. I mean it.
-Gonna act clueless, huh? -No, sir.
Did I screw up or something? What happened?
PERSONAL RECORD OF DEFECTOR TO NORTH KOREA - PARK JEONGPIL
Says here your uncle defected to the North.
Are you a spy?
A commie in Military Security Command? What's your angle?
Come on!
Are you a spy?
No, I'm not.
So…
Could I bum a smoke from you, sir?
You little shit…
I cut ties with that side of the family a long time ago.
As for my uncle…
I joined MSC before I learned about it.
How did you even get in?
The officer who hired me, uh…
expunged my file.
He erased your record, huh?
Why?
I did him one favor. And it was pretty difficult.
And in return, he fixed my record.
You're the KCIA director. You're a powerful man, right?
You probably wouldn't go through the trouble
to screw over a low-level captain.
What is it you want from me, sir?
Your mind works fast.
And there's ambition in your eyes. That's good.
There we go.
KOREAN CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
"Min Jong…"
[Kihun] It's confirmed. Colonel Baek won't be attending
the Joint Investigation Headquarters meeting.
HWANG DAESIK, JO HYEONGU, AHN JAEHO… MIN JONGHWAN, KIM DONGMIN
He'll be at a Martial Law Command meeting at Army Headquarters instead.
He'll be gone, sir.
He'll leave the building a full 30 minutes ahead of the operation.
So don't worry about him.
They're all getting together for a meeting tomorrow at the JIH, 10:00 a.m.
All you have to do is…
get the briefcase in there before the meeting starts.
You know I'll be the first one they suspect.
And even if it works,
I'm as good as dead, aren't I?
[Kitae] If you don't do it, you'll die here.
But if you succeed,
you might actually survive in the end.
I'll help you.
If it ends up working…
you better help me out.
What, you want me to make you a general?
You can kill yourself being loyal,
but without power…
you'll always be invisible.
I have to take this gamble.
-[car door closes] -[engine starts]
You know who this is?
Min Jonghwan, really?
It was him? [scoffs]
There's something else you should probably know.
Baek got explosives recently.
Word is, he's bought some before.
Do you know anything about that?
Well, it looks like you do.
[Geonyoung] Hmm…
And he's got agents standing by tomorrow.
Really?
You see?
It's all coming together.
There's a regular meeting at the JIH tomorrow, right?
Hwang Daesik will be there for sure.
Gonna be interesting.
So… what's the plan, then?
[Haksu] You better do this right.
The ground!
[Jaeho] The wounded!
[in English] Oh, what the hell!
-[Jaeho] Comrade!
-[courtesan exclaims]
[in English] What are you doing? Get out of there.
Stop it. Look what he's doing.
Someone's had a little too much to drink.
What are you looking for under there?
You're embarrassing me, you dirty old man.
-[all applauding, cheering]
-[Jaeho, in English] We are one! -[chuckling]